ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- OSH J. P. Stevens (Delta Number 4) Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1979-1983 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company (Fabricating Plant) Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company (Roanoke Number 1 Plant) Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company (Roanoke Number 2 Plant) Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens, Rosemary Plt. Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina Review Board Case, 1978-1981 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Health Violations J. P. Stevens and Company Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1977-1982 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Health Violations J. P. Stevens and Co. Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1976-1979 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens (Safety Violations) Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1975-1977 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Shelby, North Carolina, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens Company, Inc. OSHRC Docket Number 78-2738, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Stuart, Virginia, 1977-1980 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company Stuart, Virginia, 1977-1978 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- OSHA Case Sterling Textile Printing Co. Paterson, New Jersey, 1976-1983 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Suzy Curtain, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Synergistic Chemical Company, Fall River, Massachusetts, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Synthane-Taylor Corporation - II (Docket Number 79-3681) Valley Forge, Pennsylvania, 1978-1979 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Synthane-Taylor Company (subs. Alco Standard Corporation) Betzwood, Pennsylvania, 1978-1979 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Case File Seamco, Incorporated New Haven, Indiana, 1979-1985 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Sherbren Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Skydyne, Inc. Port Jervis, New York, 1980-1984 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Skyland International Corporation Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Stablex, Inc. Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Staple Prints, Inc. Hendersonville, North Carolina, 1980-1981 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Tenneford Weaving, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Tennessee Textile, Jackson, Tennessee, 1983-1986 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Textile Prints Corp. Branford, Connecticut, 1979-1983 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- OSH Case DG Trim Products, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- OSH Case True Temper Corporation, 1972-1983 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Unarco Home Products Paris, Illinois, 1981-1986 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Uniglass Company, 1977-1980 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- OSH Case United Dye and Finishing Company Raritan, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Unitog Company Clinton, Missouri, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Velourit Processors, Inc. Hoboken, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- OSHA Case Vernon Plastics Corp., 1974-1983 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Victor Balata and Textile Belting Company, Easton, Pennsylvania, 1974-1987 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- OSH Case W and M Headwear, Inc. Brooklyn, New York, 1988-1989 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- OSH Case W. S. Libby Co. Lewiston, Maine, 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Wall Industries Beverly, New Jersey, 1978-1981 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Wapakoneta Industries, Wapakoneta, Ohio, 1984-1993 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Westmont Industries, Inc. East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania, 1987-1988 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- OSH Case West Point Papperell OSHA Warrant Case Lindale, Georgia, 1977-1986 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Case West Point Pepperell OSHA Warrant Case, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- OSH Case West Point-Pepperell, Lindale, Georgia, 1975-1986 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- OSH Case West Point Pepperell, Inc. Lindale, Georgia, 1975-1984 (Box 109, Folder 21)
- Case West Point Pepperell OSHRC Cotton Dust Case, 1978-1981 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Whittaker Corporation, Providence Chemical Division, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- White Automotive Company, Colorado, 1981-1990 (Box 109, Folder 24)
- OSHA Case White Knight Manufacturing Company, Ozark, Alabama, 1971-1973 (Box 109, Folder 25)
- OSHA Case Jack Winter, Inc. Warren, Arkansas, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Wonder Knit. Co. Galax, Virginia, 1983-1984 (Box 109, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Woodbridge Foam, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 28)
- OSHA Case Worth Textile Div. Lehigh Valley Industries, Sylvester, Georgia, 1980-1983 (Box 109, Folder 29)
- OSHA Case Xcel Newark, New Jersey, 1974-1978 (Box 109, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Xerox Corporation, Pomona, California, 1985-1988 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Xerox Corp. Pomona, California, 1985-1988 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Xerox Corporation, Pomona, California, 1978-1985 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- X-Tyal International Corporation, North Adams, Massachusetts, 1982-1985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- OSHA Case X-Tyal International Corporation, Hudson, New York, 1977-1984 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Zenith Dyeing and Finishing, Paterson, New Jersey, 1981-1983 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Z.R.M. Industries, Pottsville, Pennsylvania, 1979-1986 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Asbestos State Regulations, 1968-1988 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Asbestos TWUA Activities, 1972-1974 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Asbestos U. S. General, 1968-1972 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Asbestos U. S. Government Standard, 1973-1976 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Asbestos U. S. Government Proposed Standard, 1983-1984 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Asbestos U. S. Government Proposed Standard ACTWU Testimony, 1983-1984 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Asbestos U. S. Government Proposed Standard Risk Assessment, 1983-1984 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Asbestos U. S. Government Revised Standard - Court of Appeals, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Asbestos U. S. Government Revised Standard, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Asbestos U. S. Standard, 1975-1978 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Asbestos U. S. Standards - Enforcement, 1978-1979 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Asbestos U. S. Standard I - OSHA, NIOSH, 1971-1980 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Asbestos - U. S. Standard II (Statements), 1971-1972 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Asbestos - U. S. Standard - EPA, 1971-1979 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Asbestos White Lung Association, 1982-1985 (Box 111, Folder 15)
- Asbestos - Workers' Compensation Conference, 1972-1984 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- Impact of Proposed OSHA Standard for Asbestos First Report to U. S. Department of Labor, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- Asbestos - Workmen's Compensation, 1991-1994 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- Asbestos - General Folder 1, 1976-1989 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Asbestos General Folder 2, 1979-1989 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Asbestos General, 1965-1979 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Asbestos AIA (Asbestos Information Association), 1975 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Asbestos Victims of America (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Asbestos Asten-Hill Manufacturing Company, 1968-1974 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Asbestos ILO - Documents, 1973-1986 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Asbestos ILO- Worksheets, 1973-1976 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Asbestos IUD, 1972-1975 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Asbestos Joint Research Program, 1968-1977 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Asbestos Literature I, 1965-1984 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Asbestos Literature II - Mount Sinai, 1968-1991 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Asbestos New York City, 1968-1988 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Asbestos New York Academy of Sciences Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- Asbestos New Yorker Magazine Annals of Industry, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 15)
- Asbestos Product Liability Law Suits, 1980-1994 (Box 112, Folder 16)